http://www.playattention.com/legal-terms#Privacy-Policy

Terms of Use
Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the following terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this Site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these Terms and Conditions and acknowledge that any other agreements between you and Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. are superseded and of no force or effect.
PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING OR USING THIS SITE. BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE AND SHOULD IMMEDIATELY CEASE SUCH USE. UNIQUE LOGIC AND TECHNOLOGY, INC. MAY MODIFY THIS AGREEMENT AT ANY TIME, AND SUCH MODIFICATIONS SHALL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON POSTING OF THE MODIFIED AGREEMENT ON THIS SITE. YOU AGREE TO REVIEW THE AGREEMENT PERIODICALLY TO BE AWARE OF SUCH MODIFICATIONS AND YOUR CONTINUED ACCESS OR USE OF THIS SITE SHALL BE DEEMED YOUR CONCLUSIVE ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED AGREEMENT.
Disclaimer
Play Attention® gathers and analyzes brain wave signals to provide visual and/or auditory feedback. Play Attention® is not a medical device and is not intended for use in clinical medical applications. Unique Logic & Technology, Inc. makes no warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to, any implied warranty of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. The User is responsible for determining whether this product is fit for a particular purpose. Unique Logic & Technology, Inc. makes no claims as to potential medical or therapeutic benefits. The Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. product is an integrated educational-game system for educational professionals and personal use. The system requires no intrusion into the person of the user. Play Attention is FCC certified and UL 60601-1 safety conformant.
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. makes no guarantees that its product, Play Attention® will have the same results for all users.
The material to be presented in this page and all subsidiary pages at this site includes many results which have been obtained in a educational setting, and they do not yet have grounding in research under more controlled conditions. They must therefore be regarded as preliminary.
Information on this Site is provided for informational and educational purposes. Such information is not meant to substitute for the advice of any health care provider. Never hesitate to tell your health care provider about techniques or technologies you are undertaking or intend to undertake. You should not use the information contained herein for diagnosing or treating a health problem or disease. You should read carefully all product packaging including the User’s Manual. If you have or suspect that you have a medical problem, promptly contact your health care provider. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this site. Information and statements regarding educational interventions or technologies have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration and are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease or disorder.
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may alter this site at any time without notice but does not assume any responsibility to update it. While Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. strives to include accurate and current information, we make no representations or warranties, express or implied, as to the accuracy or completeness of the information provided on this Web site and disclaim any liability for the use of this site or any site linked to it. Specifically, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. will not be liable for the accuracy, completeness, adequacy, timeliness, or comprehensiveness of the information contained on the Site. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. also assumes no responsibility, and shall not be liable for, any damages to, or viruses that may infect, your computer equipment or other property on account of your access to, use of, or browsing in the Site or your downloading of any materials, data, text, images, video, or audio from the Site. All users agree that all access and use of this Web site and on any Web site linked to from this site and the content thereof is at their own risk. Neither Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. nor any other party involved in the production, creation, or delivery of this Web site or on any Web site linked to from this site shall be liable in any manner whatsoever for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect or punitive damages arising out of your access, use or inability to use this Web site or any Web site linked to from this site, or any errors or omissions in the content thereof. The Information may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. reserves the right to make changes, corrections and/or improvements to the Information, and to the products and programs described in such information, at any time without notice.
Links
Links to third party pages are provided for convenience only. We do not express any opinion on the content of any third party pages and expressly disclaim any liability for all third party information and the use of it. Because Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. has no control over and does not endorse any of the sites to which the Site is linked and because Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. has not reviewed any or all of the sites to which the Site is linked, you acknowledge that Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. is not responsible for the content of any off-Site pages or any other sites linked to the Site. Your linking to the Site, off-Site pages or other sites is at your own risk and without the permission of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. By making use of any such links, you understand that the legal statement and privacy policy of the linked site will apply and which may be different from those of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.
Links to this Site are permitted only to the home page. Deep linking is not permitted without the prior written consent of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.
Framing of this Site by sites or site elements of parties not part of the Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. is not permitted. In-line linking or any other manner of incorporating parts of this Site in sites of parties not part of the Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. group is equally prohibited.
Site Availability
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. reserves the right to interrupt or discontinue any or all of the functionality of its Site. The Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. entity controlling this Site accepts no responsibility or liability whatsoever for any interruption or discontinuance of any or all functionality of its Site, whether the result of actions or omissions of an entity of the Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. or a third party.
Copyright Terms of Use
You may download, display or print information from this Site (the “Information”) solely for non-commercial personal use.
You must reproduce each and every copyright notice or other proprietary rights notice contained in any Information you download. You may not, however, distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, repost, or use the content of the Site for public or commercial purposes, including the text, images, audio, and video without written permission of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.. You should assume that everything you see or read on this Site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used except as provided in these Terms and Conditions or in the text on the Site without the written permission of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. neither warrants nor represents that your use of materials displayed on the Site will not infringe rights of third parties not owned by or affiliated with Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.
With the exception of the foregoing limited authorization, no license to or right in any copyright of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. or of any other party is granted or conferred to you.
The Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. Internet sites may contain or reference trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes or other proprietary rights of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc., its affiliates and/or other parties. No license to or right in any such trademarks, patents, trade secrets, technologies, products, processes and other proprietary rights of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc., its affiliates and/or other parties is granted to or conferred upon you.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.playattention.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. This Privacy Statement of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. (“Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.” “we” “us” or “our”) outlines how your personally identifiable information and other personal data (your “user information”) will be collected, used, and shared in connection with your access to and/or use of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc..com and any content, features, services, or other offerings that Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may provide in connection therewith (collectively, the “Site”). This Privacy Statement also describes your choices and rights regarding the use, access and correction or deletion of your user information. By using the Site, you consent to the use of your user information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. If you are located in the EU, you will also be asked to provide clear and unequivocal affirmative consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your user information via cookies and similar technologies. The Site is owned and operated by Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.
Notice to EU Individuals: this Privacy Statement and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR.
Summary
To enhance, personalize, and support your experience on the Site, among other things, we collect, use, and share your user information. For example, we use aggregated information to develop content targeted to user interests and to generally improve the Site's user experience. As detailed below, your user information may also be used by Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. and its partners to tailor content and ads, provide social media features (e.g., features that allow you to share content directly to your preferred social media platform), track your preferences, analyze traffic, and provide similar services and content. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. is committed to your privacy and will not share any user information with any third party without your consent, except as outlined in this Privacy Statement or as permitted by law. If you have any requests, comments, or questions about this Privacy Statement or your user information, please contact us in the manner provided below.
What this Privacy Statement Covers
This Privacy Statement covers the Site. While you may encounter links on the Site to other websites, such as those relating to our third party sponsors, advertisers, and other partners, please note that these websites are not covered by this Privacy Statement (unless otherwise noted on such site, which may be the case if, for example, the site is also owned and operated by Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.).
This Privacy Statement does not apply to the activities of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. third party sponsors, advertisers, and other partners that may collect your user information while accessing or using such third party's services in connection with your use of our Site (e.g. social media and sharing services). The privacy and information practices of those third parties are not covered by this Privacy Statement. To learn more about such third party policies, we encourage you to read and review the privacy statements of each third party service that you may choose to use in connection with the Site. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by us.
As a general reminder, please think carefully before you decide to put anything on the internet. For example, if you voluntarily disclose user information in chat areas or bulletin boards (e.g., comments sections), that information could be seen and used by others, and may result in unsolicited messages from others. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information or other user information you may choose to submit in these public forums. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us as provided below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove personal information voluntarily disclosed by you in such forums for legal retention purposes or technical limitations (e.g., the data may not be searchable), in which case, we will notify you if we are unable to do so.
Gathering of Information
We collect user information when you use the Site. Sometimes you may submit it to us yourself, other times it may be collected automatically. You can manage and change your preferences as outlined below.
Information Collected
When you use the Site, your user information may be collected, used, and shared in a variety of manners. As detailed below, the type of user information collected may vary based on how it was gathered, but may include, among other things, your name, email address, and other information that you voluntarily submit (e.g., when setting up an account or submitting a registration or application on the Site, you may submit your contact information, social media account handles, and/or professional information), information automatically collected about your usage of the Site (e.g., the content that you choose to view), and information about you that our third party partners may share with us if such third party partners have previously received your consent to do so.
Voluntary Submission
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may collect user information that is voluntarily provided by you or with your permission. For example, we may ask you for information, such as your e-mail address, when you register to become a member of the Site or register for a Unique Logic and Technology, Inc.-produced live event. You may also provide information to Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. in other contexts, including, for example, on your member profile page and public profile URL, to enter into a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion, or to apply for consideration in connection with a Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. list or similar accolade (e.g., Under 30 list applications). In the event you order something from the Site or one of our co-branded websites, we may request additional personal information, such as your address, telephone number and credit card information, in order to complete the purchase. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services. When you register or become a member of the Site or provide information to Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. in any other manner, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information. We also supplement the data you provide to us with data from data append services such as public or social graph data in order to better serve you with content or promotions.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
A cookie is a small data file that is written to your computer's hard drive by your web browser. A cookie file can contain and/or automatically collect information, such as a user identification code or IP address, that a website will use to track the pages and number of times you have visited. The data read from these cookies may be linked to personally identifying (PII) and non-personally identifying (non-PII) information.
We and our partners use cookies and similar technologies on the Site to personalize and optimize your browsing experience and the Site by:
providing you tailored content and advertisements (see below for more information),
enabling social media features,
safeguarding against spam and malware,
analyzing trends, traffic, and user behavior,
administering the website,
gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole,
tracking web and advertising analytics throughout the Site and its affiliate websites,
remembering your preferences and voluntarily-submitted information (e.g. custom video playlists, preferences, job title, story ratings, membership status),
performing location-related functionalities and analytics,
participating in market research (e.g., website ratings), and
educating ourselves about how we can continue to improve the Site and its various elements.
Cookies fall into the subcategories below.
Essential Cookies. Certain cookies are used for specific purposes that are essential to your secure use and navigation of the Site. Without them, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may not be able to provide core Site functions and features to you, and the Site would not operate as well as you or Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. would like. These cookies collect and use information such as your server preferences, single-session data and corresponding identifier, web beacons and log files (detailed below), and other credential-related information. For EU individuals, essential cookies also help inform Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. whether you require, or have already been served, an affirmative consent request in connection with the GDPR. Essential cookies include analytics cookies, which provide us data that allows Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. to better understand its users and improve the Site based on what we have learned from that data.
Preference Cookies. Other cookies are used to collect and process information about your preferences and similar choices in connection with the Site in order to optimize your browsing experience (e.g., various local preference settings; which geographically-customized version of the Site and related content you may prefer [e.g., Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. US, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. Asia, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. Europe]). Preference cookies include social media cookies, which collect information about your social media usage and other data you may have provided in connection with such usage (if you access the Site through a social media website or mobile application, you may have social media cookies). If you wish to modify or change your social media cookies, please visit and review the settings on your applicable social media account(s).
Advertising Cookies. To help support the Site and further tailor your experience, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. and its advertising partners (and/or their third party analytics providers) also use cookies on the Site to personalize the content and advertisements you may be shown. Such advertisements use cookies to provide you targeted advertisements that may be more consistent with your interests than non-targeted advertisements. Certain Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. advertising partners may also use cookies to monitor or track the performance of their advertising content, including native advertising content. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. does not provide user information to advertising partners except in connection with the Site or as required by law.
If you would like to manage your cookie preferences or learn more information about this practice and your right to decline (or opt-out of) cookies placed by some or all of these companies by selecting to accept or decline cookies when prompted by the site.
We encourage you to consider keeping your cookies enabled, as if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Site, you may not be able to use or benefit from certain features of the Site, particularly the features that are designed to personalize your experience.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but generally allow users to modify their browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, to accept cookies only from certain websites, and/or to refuse all cookies.
Web Beacons
We may use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) on our sites in order to recognize users, assess traffic patterns, identify preferred content and measure site engagement. We, at times, may also include web beacons in our e-mail messages, including newsletters, in order to count how many e-mail messages have been opened.
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. and its partners (including advertising partners) also may use web beacons to collect various data provided by your browser while you are on our Site and elsewhere (i.e., outside of the Site) where we may be acting as a 3rd party. This data is collected in the aggregate, but may include or be associated with other non-PII or PII that users have voluntarily submitted.
Log Files
The Site's web and ad servers log information about a user's IP address, browser type and the current URL the user is requesting. This information is always provided by a user's browser and automatically logged by most websites. These log files are stored in a secure location and used in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our website.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. Any information, communication or material you transmit to the Site by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and nonproprietary. Anything you transmit or post becomes the property of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. or its affiliates and may be used for any purpose, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast and posting. Furthermore, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to the Site for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products using such information.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Our primary goal in collecting, using, and sharing user information is to enhance your experience on the Site, support the Site, and improve its features, performance, and other elements. Your user information may be used for the purposes outlined below. We will not use your user information without a valid legal basis to do so.
To Target Content and Advertising
To develop and provide content and advertising to you that is targeted to your interests, we use the analytics collected by the systems described above to determine which areas of our website you prefer based upon the frequency of your visits and engagement with those areas. We may make reasonable assumptions based on your browser provided data to target relevant content and advertising to you on our site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a 3rd party. We may also make reasonable geographic and demographic assumptions based on your presented IP address to target relevant content and advertising.
To Provide Interactive Communications from the Site
To enhance your experience we may provide you with interactive communications, such as notifications of activity by topic or contributor to the e-mail address that you provide to us. Such interactive communications are provided only to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive them as part of their user profile.
From time to time we may provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the website to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to send such communications as part of their user profile.
To Provide Communications from Third Parties
We respect the privacy of our users and will not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor will we permit anyone else to do so.
Sharing of Information
You may be requested to voluntarily provide certain user information during your use of the Site. If you choose to do so, that user information may be shared with Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for Unique Logic and Technology, Inc..
We use third parties to provide credit card processing, e-mail service providers and hosting services on the Site. When you sign up for such services, we will share your user information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your user information for any other purpose. With respect to credit card processing, we do not collect, store, or process any credit card information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service.
In addition, if you provide any personally identifiable information via an advertiser promotion, please be aware you are directly providing your personally identifiable information to that advertiser.
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you, such as your name and e-mail. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use this personally identifiable information to notify contest winners and award prizes.
We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.
As noted above, you can log in to our site using sign-in services that bridge your social media login information with the Site. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. These services give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network. The Site includes social media features, widgets and/or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features are small content modules that users can embed on sites and may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, or set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
We offer widgets that are hosted on the Site, like our embeddable video player. Use of the www.playattention.com widgets is subject to the Site terms of use, but downloading or embedding these widgets on other websites is not covered by this privacy statement.
Privacy with Service Providers
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of newsletter mailings, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service. In some instances, these companies may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the external service provider. In all cases, these companies are subject to agreements that require them to maintain the confidentiality of your information and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
In the Event of Sale or Bankruptcy
The ownership of the Site may change at some point in the future. Should that occur, we want this site to be able to maintain a relationship with you. In the event of a sale, merger, public offering, bankruptcy or other change in control of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc., your information may be shared with the person or business that owns or controls this site. Opting out of receiving information from third parties will not affect our right to transfer your information to a new owner, but your choices will continue to be respected regarding the use of your information. You will be notified as described below in "How will I know if the Privacy Statement is changed."
As Required By Law
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law such as to comply with a subpoena or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. or to protect and defend the rights or property of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc..
Notice to EU Individuals: As outlined in this Privacy Statement, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. will not process your user information without a lawful basis to do so, as such bases are defined in Article 6 of the GDPR. In general, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. will process your user information on the legal bases of consent, contract (if you have entered into an agreement with us and such processing is a necessary part thereof), or legal obligation (as noted above). Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may also process certain user information on the basis of the following legitimate interests, provided that such interests are not overridden by your privacy rights and interests: delivering and continuing to develop and improve the Site, learning from your behavior on the Site (e.g., analyzing traffic) to better serve you and other Site users, helping us modify or enhance the Site and its content, receiving insight as to what users do (and don't) like about our Site or aspects thereof, and providing a stable, consistent, and secure user experience in connection with the Site.
Security
We care about the protection of your user information and use industry standard safeguards to do so. Of course, it's important to keep in mind that no data transmission on the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Your information is stored on Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. servers located in the United States. We use industry standard physical, electronic, and organizational safeguards to protect your user information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. If you are concerned that your privacy may have been breached, please contact us as provided below.
Privacy of Children
The Site is intended for people who are at least 16 years of age. If you are less than 16 years old, please do not send any user information to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect (nor do we wish to collect) any personally identifiable information or other user information from children under the age of 16. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 16, we will delete that information from our database and terminate the corresponding account, if any. We encourage you to discuss the Site with your parent or guardian.
Cross-border Transfers
Your user information may be transferred to other countries in connection with your use of the Site. If you access or use the Site outside of the United States, your user information will be transferred to our servers in the United States.
How to Contact Us
Please contact us if you have any questions or requests. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or how to remove or modify your user information or related consents, please feel free to contact us telephone at 828.676.2240 or the mailing address below. Our mailing address is Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. PO Box 2147, Skyland, NC 28776. You may also email us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
How Will I Know if the Privacy Statement Is Changed?
If we make any material changes and you have submitted your email address on the Site,  we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Note on Translated Version(s): For your convenience, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may make translated versions of this Privacy Statement available on the Site. In the event that the terms of any such translated version conflict with the terms of the English version, the terms of the English version of this Privacy Statement will control in all instances.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Although Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. may from time to time monitor or review discussions, chats, postings, transmissions, bulletin boards, and the like on the Site, Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the content of any such locations nor for any error, defamation, libel, slander, omission, falsehood, obscenity, pornography, profanity, danger, or inaccuracy contained in any information within such locations on the Site. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law. Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such information or materials.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. While we do not collect credit card information on this site, some personal information may be volunteered by you such as address and telephone information when you request a CD or other information. This information is stored on a secured server and is protected offline.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800.788.6786 or via email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Products and Services
Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. Internet sites may contain information on its worldwide products and services, not all of which are available in every location. A reference to a Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. product or service on a Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. Internet site does not imply that such product or service is or will be available in your location. You should rely on product information especially created for your location. That information can be found on the Internet sites of the Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. affiliates in your location.
Patents
Play Attention® is patented. Patents No. 6,097,981, 6,402,520, and 6,626,676 B2. Others pending.
NASA
Unique Logic has incorporated certain clarifying references to “NASA” that have been reviewed and approved by NASA Patent Counsel as of July 8, 2006
Trademarks
Play Attention® is a registered trademark of Unique Logic and Technology, Inc. BodyWave® is a registered trademark Freer Logic, Inc.
Better Business Bureau
Play Attention was established in 1994. Play Attention has received an A+ rating from the Better Business Bureau as the pioneer and innovator of neurocognitive technology for over 24 years.
Space Foundation
Play Attention has more than  10 years of partnership with the Space Foundation through the Space Certification program. Play Attention is proud to carry the Certified Space Technology and Educational seal from the Space Foundation.
